<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Cafe1_name">CT Coffee and Coconuts</string>
    <string name="Cafe1_description">A special place where you can enjoy a snack and a drink all day long. Where there was still a cinema in the 1920s, you can now settle down on a bean bag and enjoy various home-made dishes and drinks. The menu is extensive and for any time of the day. You can even have breakfast all day at CT Coffee &amp; Coconuts if you wish. Start the day with a coffee and coconut pancakes, recover after exercise with a juice or fresh coconut water, or stop by for a (late) lunch. Don\'t have time during the day? In the evening there is also plenty of choice for drinks and dinner. All this in an imposing space that is very tastefully decorated; no reason to pass by when you are in the Pijp!</string>
    <string name="Cafe1_address">Ceintuurbaan 282–284, 1072 GK Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Cafe1_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.352607,4.891426</string>
    <string name="Cafe2_name">Back to Black</string>
    <string name="Cafe2_description">Back to Black is a speciality coffee bar and concept store in Amsterdam, selling art and design products alongside high quality coffee and cakes. On a quaint canalside corner a short stroll away from Leidseplein, this cute cafe is the perfect place to while away a morning with friends or a good book, whilst you indulge in homemade delicacies from the kitchen. The owners sell only art and products designed and made in the Netherlands, employing a sustainable local for local ethos. An oasis in the heart of Amsterdam.</string>
    <string name="Cafe2_address">Weteringstraat 48, 1017 SP Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Cafe2_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.361047,4.888568</string>
    <string name="Cafe3_name">Café de Prins</string>
    <string name="Cafe3_description">Café de Prins is located on one of the most beautiful parts of the Prinsengracht. Leaning against the Jordaan with the Westerkerk and the Anne Frank House opposite, it is surrounded by history. What was once a coffee and tea shop became Café de Prins in 1967. The Prince grew into a household name in Amsterdam and became a magnet for craftsmen, students and artists, for local residents and tourists, for young and old. You can go to Café de Prins to start your day with a delicious breakfast, for lunch, for a tasty bar snack, for an extensive dinner or for a drink.</string>
    <string name="Cafe3_address">Prinsengracht 124, 1015 EA Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Cafe3_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.376163,4.88411</string>
    <string name="Restaurant1_name">Restaurant De Kas</string>
    <string name="Restaurant1_description">In a striking greenhouse in Amsterdam-Oost, you’ll find Restaurant de Kas, a unique restaurant that embodies the art of eating according to nature\'s rhythms. With its emphasis on seasonal and locally sourced ingredients, Restaurant de Kas offers a sustainable dining experience like no other. Since opening its doors in 2001, de Kas has pioneered the farm-to-table movement, serving a menu that evolves with the seasons and showcases the freshest harvests from its own gardens and local farms. The dishes feature pure, simple ingredients, and with a Red as well as a Green Michelin star under their belts, it comes as no surprise that these ingredients are of the highest quality.</string>
    <string name="Restaurant1_address">Kamerlingh Onneslaan 3, 1097 DE Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Restaurant1_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.352292,4.930352</string>
    <string name="Restaurant2_name">Ciel Bleu Restaurant</string>
    <string name="Restaurant2_description">In the two-star restaurant Ciel Bleu Restaurant, on the 23rd floor of Hotel Okura Amsterdam, it\'s all about details and everything comes together to perfection. The dishes, the wines, the ambiance and the personal service make a visit to Ciel Bleu a special gastronomic experience with a panoramic view of Amsterdam. The spectacular view over Amsterdam offers the perfect opportunity to see the city from a different perspective. Head Chef Arjan Speelman and his team will surprise you with refined, culinary creations in combination with the best wine suggestions and elegant service.</string>
    <string name="Restaurant2_address">Ferdinand Bolstraat 333, 1072 LH Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Restaurant2_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.34881,4.893638</string>
    <string name="Restaurant3_name">Restaurant Vinkeles</string>
    <string name="Restaurant3_description">The 2-Michelin-starred Restaurant Vinkeles is a special destination in the center of Amsterdam. Located in a sunken 18th century bakery building, it is the perfect location to enjoy the craftsmanship of Chef Jurgen van der Zalm and his team. On a never-ending quest to bring out the flavors, purity and character of first-class ingredients, Jurgen van der Zalm has elevated his kitchen to the highest culinary level imaginable, characterized by French cooking techniques. It is not without reason that Vinkeles is the proud bearer of 2 Michelin stars.</string>
    <string name="Restaurant3_address">Keizersgracht 384, 1016 GB Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Restaurant3_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.36929,4.884014</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly1_name">Nemo Science Museum</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly1_description">Right next to the Central Station is one of the most modern architectural highlights of Amsterdam. NEMO Science Museum, the large, green building houses the largest science museum in the Netherlands. The building was designed by the famous Italian architect Renzo Piano. From the roof square you can admire a magnificent view of Amsterdam. NEMO Science Museum is the largest Science museum in the Netherlands, created for anyone with a curious mind. Visitors of all ages are welcome to discover the world of science and technology. NEMO takes you into the wonders of the everyday. Discover, for example, how bridges work, why you sometimes see things that are not there and what causes lightning, in the interactive exhibits. Workshops, videos, experiments and demonstrations complement the NEMO experience. A crackling sweater or a rainbow: you will see the world around you as never before after a visit to NEMO.</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly1_address">Oosterdok 2, 1011 VX Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly1_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.374238,4.912014</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly2_name">Artis Amsterdam Royal Zoo</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly2_description">Fantastic news from ARTIS. On Friday afternoon, August 16, a healthy baby giraffe was born. The birth went smoothly, and within two hours, the calf was standing and nursing from its mother. The ARTIS team is relieved and happy. The birth is great news for the European breeding program for this endangered species. Be surprised by the many animal species that live with and among each other in the Monkey House and Bird House. Discover the tiniest organisms in ARTIS-Micropia, the world\'s first microbe museum. Travel through space in the Planetarium. View the giraffes together with zebras and springboks on the Savannah.</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly2_address">Plantage Kerklaan 38–40, 1018 CZ Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly2_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.366101,4.916811</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly3_name">The Pancake Bakery</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly3_description">A cozy pancake house located in a 17th-century VOC canal house on the Prinsengracht in Amsterdam. The Pancake Bakery started as a small pancake restaurant with a basic menu. In 1980 the owner (still the current owner) made several changes that made The Pancake Bakery what it is today: a world famous pancake restaurant that everyone loves. Some features of the restaurant include the open kitchen, the famous "international" pancakes whose ingredients are based on various dishes from all over the world, and the jars of real syrup on every table that you can enjoy generously!</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly3_address">Prinsengracht 191, 1015 DS Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Kids_Friendly3_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.378592,4.887001</string>
    <string name="Park1_name">Vondelpark</string>
    <string name="Park1_description">The Vondelpark is Amsterdam\'s most popular park, attracting thousands of tourists, residents and everyone in between every day. Amsterdam\'s Vondelpark is home to a selection of restaurants and cafés, including the Blauwe Theehuis, Café Vertigo, Vondelpark3, De Vondeltuin and the Groot Melkhuis. You’ll also find a skate rental shop, an open-air theatreand a rose garden with more than 70 types of roses in the park. The Vondelpark was designed by landscape architect L.D. Zocher and has been awarded national heritage status.</string>
    <string name="Park1_address">Vondelpark, 1071 AA Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Park1_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.357994,4.868648</string>
    <string name="Park2_name">The Amsterdamse Bos</string>
    <string name="Park2_description">Located on the edge of the city, the Amsterdamse Bos (Amsterdam Forest) is Amsterdam’s largest park and recreational area. The lush forests and grassy meadows offer plenty of space for a relaxing picnic with family or friends, and the park is crossed by many kilometres of well-marked walking and cycling paths. From the Museumplein it is only 20 minutes by bike and then you are in Het Amsterdamse Bos. Did you know that the Amsterdamse Bos is 3x times bigger than Central Park in New York and that it attracts about 6 million visitors every year. In addition to the many cultural events in the Bostheater, you can also enjoy many national and international sporting events in the Amsterdamse Bos.</string>
    <string name="Park2_address">Bosbaanweg 5, 1182 AG Amstelveen</string>
    <string name="Park2_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.326659,4.849391</string>
    <string name="Park3_name">Oosterpark</string>
    <string name="Park3_description">The Oosterpark is a large city park located in Amsterdam Oost. This open green space is filled with ponds and streams, a wading pool for children and plenty of walking paths. Considered Amsterdam’s most multicultural park, it draws a diverse local crowd and hosts a variety of festivals throughout the summer. There is also a speaker\'s stone, where people speak their minds every Sunday at 13:00.</string>
    <string name="Park3_address">Oosterpark, 1092 AT Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Park3_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.359958,4.920328</string>
    <string name="Shopping1_name">De Bijenkorf department store</string>
    <string name="Shopping1_description">De Bijenkorf luxury department store is a true institution of fashion and style. Defining taste and setting trends since 1870, this department store now stands in an enviable location on Amsterdam’s Dam Square. What started 140 years ago as a small haberdashery shop has since grown into the Netherlands’ largest premium department store. De Bijenkorf carries the best fashion brands, designer brands and luxury products: everything you can think of, from the latest beauty products to stunning accessories and from exquisite dinnerware to the most adorable toys. You can even buy heavenly handmade chocolates. De Bijenkorf offers the highest quality standard and always presents the latest trends, the most spectacular events and outstanding premium services.</string>
    <string name="Shopping1_address">Dam 1, 1012 JS Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Shopping1_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.373561,4.894367</string>
    <string name="Shopping2_name">Magna Plaza</string>
    <string name="Shopping2_description">Magna Plaza is an indoor shopping centre located in a historical building behind the Royal Palace. Built at the end of the 19th century, this former post office is now an exclusive shopping destination with more than 20 stores plus a new exhibition space spread over four floors. From clothes and shoes to jewellery and hair salons, the Magna Plaza indoor shopping centre has an excellent variety of shops. Just a few of the brands you’ll find here include Mango, Swarovski, gsus and Lacoste. When it’s time for a break, you can stop at Grand Café Ovidius for a sandwich or cup of coffee. Magna Plaza is worth a visit just for the neo-Gothic architecture and impressive interior – combining classical grandeur with a modern shopping experience.</string>
    <string name="Shopping2_address">Nieuwezijds Voorburgwal 182, 1012 SJ Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Shopping2_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.373647,4.890439</string>
    <string name="Shopping3_name">De Nine Straatjes</string>
    <string name="Shopping3_description">The area between the Singel, Herengracht, Keizersgracht and Prinsengracht contains an intimate shopping area known as ‘De Negen Straatjes’ (The Nine Streets). These picturesque streets connecting the canals are filled with one-of-a-kind boutiques, stylish cafés and galleries. The New York Times describes Amsterdam’s Nine Streets as ‘a charming mixture of designer boutiques, art galleries, vintage clothing stores, gift shops and places to eat and drink’ and with good reason. This part of the city centre, tucked away behind the Royal Palace on Dam Square, is popular among shoppers hunting for specialty products and unique gifts. The streets are a paradise for pedestrians, offering idyllic views of the city’s 17th century architecture and Canal Belt, a UNESCO World Heritage Site.</string>
    <string name="Shopping3_address">Tussen de Leidsestraat en Raadhuistraat, 1016 GJ Amsterdam</string>
    <string name="Shopping3_address_url">https://www.google.com/maps/place/52.36916,4.883353</string>
    <string name="googleMaps">Show in Google Maps</string>
    <string name="navigation_back">Back</string>
</resources>